estimation180.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for checking out my privacy policy.    
Your privacy is of the utmost importance to me and I have great respect for your privacy. The intention of my education-based site and services is to provide a safe place for everyone who visits and interacts with me. This policy explains how I protect your privacy, how I treat your personal information and how it applies to both current and former visitors. For the sake of this policy, “Personal information” here means anything I know about you personally including the data I collect below.  
  
 **Data I Collect and Why I Collect It**  
In an effort to better understand who is visiting my website and to provide a better overall experience, I collect the following data:

  * Your name (so I can send you emails directed to you specifically)
  * Email address (so I know where to send the emails)
  * What resources you’ve downloaded (so I can send you tailored content specific to your interests)
  * When you signed up for my emails (so I know what content you may have already seen)
  * Your zip code and time zone (so I can let you know about events in your area)

**  
​How I Collect This Data**  
Your name, email address, and zip code are only collected if you have typed them in yourself such as when signing up for my email list or when downloading my resources that prompted you to enter your name, email address, and zip code. Your data is stored on MailChimp which is the company I use to send out my emails. However, some of your data might be stored on Google if you submit an estimate using one of the embedded Google Forms. I have and will never ask for full names, email addresses, or other private information through the use of Google Forms.

  **How Long I Hold On To This Data**  
I send regular emails to people on my list that include ideas, workshops, or special offers and will continue to use your information indefinitely to provide the best possible service. You may opt out of receiving these emails at any time by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email or by emailing me at [mr.stadel@estimation180.com](mailto:mr.stadel@estimation180.com).  
   
 **How I Keep Your Data Safe**  
I use encrypted 256-bit SSL encryption protocols and two-factor authentication behind a username and password combination. It is important to realize though that there is no such thing as perfect safety and security on the Internet.

 **I Do Not Share Your Data**  
I will never share your data with anyone. Never. I will not share your data with anyone. I treat your data with the same good-hearted and respectful intentions that I would expect anyone to treat my data. Again, you can “opt out” any time by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email or by emailing me at [mr.stadel@estimation180.com](mailto:mr.stadel@estimation180.com).

 **Pay Attention and Use Your Best Judgement**  
Never assume people are who they say they are, know what they say they know, or are affiliated with whom they say they are in the comments section or in any user-generated content area. Information obtained, read, or seen in the comments may not be reliable. I cannot be responsible for the content or accuracy of any information other visitors share, and shall not be responsible for any decisions you make based on such information. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online, for example, via the comments section, that information can be collected and used by people you don’t know. While I strive to protect your personal information and privacy, I cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online; you make such disclosures at your own risk. For example, never enter private information into the embedded Google Forms as that information is shared publicly in the linked Google Sheets.  
   
Please be careful while browsing the Internet. You should be aware that when you are on my website, you could be directed to other sites that I don’t own or control. For example, if you click on a link or a search result, the click may take you off this website. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors, and content partners that may use my logo(s) as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, solicit personal information, or contain information that you may find inappropriate or offensive. In addition, advertisers may send cookies to users that I do not control. I reserve the right to disable links from any third party sites at any time.

I do not make any representations or warranties as to the security of any information (including, without limitation, credit card and other personal information) you might be requested to give.  I strongly encourage you to make whatever investigation you feel necessary or appropriate before proceeding with any online or offline transaction.

You are entirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your information and for all activities that occur under your account. You hereby indemnify, defend and hold me and my affiliates and my officers, directors, owners, agents, information providers, affiliates, licensors and licensees (collectively, the Indemnified Parties) harmless from and against any and all liabilities and costs (including reasonable attorneys fees) incurred by the Indemnified Parties in connection with any claim arising out of any breach by you of this Agreement or claims arising from your account. You shall use your best efforts to cooperate with me in the defense of any claim. I reserve the right, at my own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you.

 **Cookies**  
My website uses cookies and log files to: (a) store information on your computer so that you will not have to re-enter it during your next visit to the Website; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our services; and (d) monitor metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed.

 **Questions**  
If you have any questions about this policy, please contact me at [mr.stadel@estimation180.com](mailto:mr.stadel@estimation180.com).

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If I make any material changes, I will notify you as required by law.
